It‘s very common these days for people to have a gym regime.
如今，人们制定健身计划是很常见的事。
Whatever the drive behind it, whether health-related, performance-related or just plain vainglory, it is not uncommon for people to take some sort of regular exercise each week.
无论背后的驱动力是什么，是与健康相关、与运动表现相关，还是仅仅出于虚荣，人们每周进行某种定期锻炼并不罕见。
But if you’ve never done it before, what‘s the best way to go about it?
但如果你以前从未进行过健身，最好的方法是什么呢？
Well, many people make use of using a PT - that’s a personal trainer.
嗯，很多人会聘请PT，也就是个人健身教练。
This might be because they‘re wet behind the ears or maybe they just don’t want the aggro of designing their own workout plan.
这可能是因为他们缺乏经验，或者也许他们只是不想自己设计健身计划那么麻烦。
A PT will create a bespoke plan for you based on your aims.
私人教练会根据你的目标为你制定一个量身定制的计划。
They will tailor it to your current abilities and, better still, they will teach you how to move in a way that won‘t incapacitate you.
他们会根据你目前的能力进行定制，更好的是，他们会教你如何以一种不会让你受伤的方式进行运动。
However, the trade-off of getting a PT is the cost.
然而，请私人教练的弊端在于费用。
With the double whammy of paying for a PT and gym membership, the price of an hourly session can be steep.
考虑到既要支付私人教练的费用，又要支付健身房的会员费这种双重负担，每小时的课程费用可能会很昂贵。
If you‘re strapped for cash, then regular sessions might be out of your budget.
如果你手头拮据，那么定期的课程可能会超出你的预算。
So what’s left?
那么还有什么选择呢？
Well, if you have the grit for it, you can make your own regime.
嗯，如果你有毅力，你可以制定自己的健身计划。
It‘s relatively easy to do if you have the know-how.
如果你具备专业知识，做起来会相对容易。
But before you do, here are some basic pointers.
但在你开始之前，这里有一些基本的要点。
First, keep your fitness goal in mind.
首先，要牢记你的健身目标。
Are you looking to slim down, bulk up, get shredded or increase your abilities?
你是想减肥、增肌、练出肌肉线条还是提高你的能力呢？
Whatever it is, make sure the things you choose to do are in pursuit of that goal.
无论目标是什么，确保你选择做的事情是为了追求这个目标。
Next, do your research.
其次，做些研究。
These days, social media is chock-full of fitness videos and advice.
如今，社交媒体上充满了健身视频和建议。
Watch as many of these as possible, but make sure to be a little critical of them — everyone has a different physique and what works for one may not work for another.
尽可能多地观看这些内容，但要确保对它们保持一定的批判性——每个人的体质都不同，对一个人有效的方法可能对另一个人却并不适用。
Finally, keep your feet on the ground.
最后，要脚踏实地。
Be patient with yourself and set realistic goals — it takes at least three months to see any realistic body changes.
对自己要有耐心，设定现实的目标——至少需要三个月才能看到身体有任何明显的变化。
And don‘t be overzealous — never work in pain — a good workout is difficult and challenging, but never painful.
而且不要过于狂热——绝不要在疼痛的情况下锻炼——一次好的锻炼是困难且具有挑战性的，但绝不是痛苦的。
Pain means you are damaging yourself.
疼痛意味着你在伤害自己。
If nothing else, focus on calisthenics — these are the basic body movements which everyone can do anywhere, even at home.
如果没有别的选择，那就专注于徒手健身——这些是每个人在任何地方都能做的基本身体动作，甚至在家里也可以。
They include squats, push-ups, pull-ups and crunches, among other things.
它们包括深蹲、俯卧撑、引体向上和仰卧起坐等等。
Do as many of one exercise as you can without stopping, and then try and repeat that number twice more — make sure you sweat, and don‘t forget to rest for a minute in between!
尽可能多地不间断地做一种运动，然后再尝试重复同样的次数两次——确保你出汗了，而且不要忘记在中间休息一分钟！